Facilities Management Records UA021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Buildings and Grounds, 1849 -- 1994; UA021.001; 8.95 Linear Feet; 68 Digital Object(s)
  - Art objects, Treasures of Tufts Exhibit, 1979; UA021.001.017.00003 (Box 17)
- Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1896 -- 2004; UA021.002; 3.85 Linear Feet; 3 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of architectural drawings and plans, and artistic renderings of Tufts University buildings.
  This series is not arranged
  - Artist paintings, UA021.002.018.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 8)
    Contains paintings of a new student residential hall, the Science and Technology Center, the Olin Center for Language and Culture and The Aidekman Art Center. Drawings were originally mounted in foam board and each had a paper label. Mounting was removed and original labels were retained.
    Science and Technology Center; Olin Center; Dormitories; paintings (visual works)
  - Tufts College in Medford and Boston Massachusetts, map, 1950; UA021.002.018.00002 (Box 18)
    This date is approximate. This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in Spring of 2009. The artist, Ernest Dudley Chase, has signed the map.
    Maps; Maps
  - Tufts College in Medford and Boston Massachusetts, map, 1950; UA021.002.018.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 8)
    This date is approximate. This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in the Spring of 2009. The artist, Ernest Dudley Chase, has signed the map. There is slight water damage at the corners.
  - Science center, 1988; UA021.002.019.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 8)
    Elevation plan, planting plan and the floor plan
    Science and Technology Center; architectural drawings (visual works)
  - Downing Hall, UA021.002.020.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 8)
    Perspective view mounted on foam board and two glossy drawings.
    Downing Hall; architectural drawing (visual works)
  - Tisch Library, 1994; UA021.002.021.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 8)
    Painting with note: Construction July '94 Completed Fall '96; mounted on foam core; originally double matted with label. Mat was moldy and was removed as much as possible. Date is approximate
    Tisch Library; paintings (visual works)
  - General Clinics drawings (first and second year), 1967; UA021.002.023.00001 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 8)
    This folder moved from the Artifact Collection, AC-34, which as subsequently dissolved.
    Medical and Veterinary Building; Dental Health Sciences Tower
  - Cabot Intercultural Center Phase Two Construction Document, 2004; UA021.002.024.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7)
    Buildings; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Facilities
  - Hillel Center Negative, 1993; UA021.002.025.00001 (Box 25)
    Negatives of photographs of artist rendings for multiple buildings: Hillel Center, Tisch Library, Cousens Athletic Center, Veterinary Education Center; donated by Rocco Carzo 2007-10
    negatives
  - Cousens Athletic Complex, Franklin M. Loew Veterinary Medical Education Center, and Tisch Library negatives and Related Correspondence, 1992-94, 1992 -- 1994; UA021.002.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Tufts University site map, 1985-08-31; UA021.002.026.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7)
    Maps
  - Dormitory blueprints, 1896; UA021.002.027.00001 (Box Shared 128)
    This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in the Spring of 2009. Note its location, it is housed in a box with other oversized materials. Inclued in this item are blurprints for the the Library Dormitory, East Hall, West Hall, Dean Hall, Theological School Dormitory, and the Women's Dormitory. Also included are the rates for the yearly cost of the room for students as well as dormitory regulations. When the bound collection of blueprints was found attached to the first page was a plan for Dean Hall and Curtis Hall on linen. The rusty paperclips attaching the plans to the bound blue prints have been removed.
    blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Chase map of Tufts College in Medford and Boston, 1955 -- 1963; UA021.002.028.00001; Chase, Ernest Dudley (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    Medford Campus; Boston Campus; Maps; Chase, Ernest Dudley, 1878-; Tufts College
  - Lefavour Map of Tufts College in Medford and Boston, 1920 -- 1945; UA021.002.028.00002; Lefavour, R.W.
    Medford Campus; Boston Campus; Maps; Tufts College
  - Map of Tufts College, 1929; UA021.002.028.00003; Blanchard Printing Co.
    Medford Campus; Maps; Tufts College
  - Supplement materials, 1920 -- 1963; UA021.002.028.00004
    Has quadrant views of the Dudley-chase maps and alternate format to the LaFavour and Alma mater maps.
    Medford (Mass.)
  - Aidekman Arts Center, 1988; UA021.002.029.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
  - Aidekman Arts Center, 1988; UA021.002.030.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
  - City Center and 11 Talbot, 1979 -- 1988; UA021.002.031.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 4)
- Additional accessions, UA021.000234
  - Facilities, service guide, UA021-001 (Box 1)
  - Reports and plans, 1979 -- 2001; UA021-002 (Box 2)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Reports and plans, 1980 -- 1990; UA021-003 (Box 3)
  - Slides and prints, 1980 -- 2000; UA021-004 (Box 4)
  - Plan of the land of Timothy Cotting transferred to Tufts College, 1869, 1937; UA021-005 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 9)